btwholesale.com 2002-02-15

# BT Wholesale.com | Welcome

| 

| 

**BT Wholesale.com Privacy Policy**

We have developed this policy because we want you to feel confident about the privacy and security of your personal information.

**Use of personal information**

Because BT Wholesale.com contains so much information, we want to help you find what you want as quickly and smoothly as possible. The more we know about you, the easier it is for us to help you. We encourage you to register so that we can give you quicker and better access to your favourite services in the future - as well as point you in directions which may interest you.

If you do register, you only have to give us your e-mail address and a password. Your e-mail address and other personal details are needed if you want to use particular online services, or to customise your use of BT Wholesale.com to suit your individual needs.  
  
---  

  * Help you to get more out of your visits to BT Wholesale.com - by suggesting information, products and services 
  * Ensure that the relevant business related information is directed to you within the site
  * Save you having to keep giving us the same information for different BT services. For instance, if you have ever ordered online with BT, certain parts of the order form may be automatically filled in for you in future.
  * Keep BT Wholesale.com up to date to offer you products and services that may interest you, by post, telephone contact or e-mail. 

If you register, we will treat you as having consented to our using your personal data in the manner described in this Policy. If you do not register, the personal data we collect from you will be limited to that which you give us in order to enter into any transactions on-line. BT Wholesale.com will use that data in order to facilitate that transaction and for no other purpose. **Email addresses**

At BT we respect the privacy of e-mail accounts and we store your e-mail addresses just as securely as other personal information on BT Wholesale.com.

We will use e-mail to send you messages with details of products and services that may be of interest to you. We may also use e-mail to keep you up to date with news about your current services, as well as anything you show an interest in, either online, or through other contact with BT Wholesale. If you do not want to be kept informed in this way by e-mail, please let us know. You can do this by ticking the relevant box on the registration form when you register for the portal, or in 'Update Your Profile' which can be found on most pages after you have logged in.

 **Right of access to your BT Wholesale information**

When you visit BTWholesale.com you have direct control over information in your personal profile. You can access and change this information at any time by using the 'update Profile' link which appears on various pages after you log in.

**Security**

We at BT are serious about guarding the security of your personal data and the details of any transactions you make.

Your password is a sensitive piece of information. Please be sure to keep this information safe and do not share it with others.

If you forget your password for any reason, you will be asked to complete a password security question which you would have decided on during your original registration process.

**How does BT protect your data?**

When you register details with us, or make an order, we use a secure server. Any data you give us is encrypted using a 'Secure Socket Layer' (SSL) session. SSL is an industry standard and is one of the best ways to ensure Internet messages are not intercepted. You should be aware, however, that older browsers cannot use SSL. To be sure, you will need Netscape version 4.05 or Microsoft Internet Explorer browsers, version 4 or above.  
Over and above what BT do to safeguard your privacy and security, there are a number of things you can do to protect yourself from Internet fraud:  

  * Choose a password you can remember but others will not guess, change it regularly, and if you do write it down, keep it somewhere safe and secure. 
  * When you have finished your session on BTWholesale.com, make sure that you prevent your details being seen by anyone that you do not wish to see them. So, if you have registered and logged in, remember to log off. Clear any 'cache' so there is no record of any transactions left on screen - both Netscape and Internet Explorer let you do this. We also recommend you then close your browser so any history of the session is cleared. As an extra precaution your session on many BTWholesale.com will 'time out' if you have not used the site for 30 minutes. 

**Use of Cookies**

BT websites create a 'cookie' when you first register online. A 'cookie' is a piece of information, like a tag, which some websites create against your PC. Our 'cookie' stores some basic information which helps us to identify if you have visited the site before and if you receive some personalised content such as your personal Quicklinks or by welcoming you by name if you have supplied this in a previous visit. However, as it is based on your PC, we will not find the 'cookie' if you visit BT Wholesale.com from a different PC to the one you registered on.

 **BT's use of 'cookies' includes the following assurances:**  

  * No information regarding your telephone number, account or payment details is included in the cookie or can be accessed using it.
  * They do not collect any information regarding the use of your PC or Internet browsing in any way. 

If you do not want a cookie to be created on your PC, web browsers such as Netscape and Internet Explorer provide the option to disable them. Please bear in mind that some personalised services on BT.com may not be available if you choose to disable cookies.

**Third party sites**

Third party Internet sites that you can link to through BTWholesale.com are not covered by our Privacy and Security policy, so we urge you to be careful when you enter any personal information online. BT Wholesale Services & Solutions accepts no responsibility or liability for these sites.

**Managing your contact with BT Wholesale**

If you would like to stop unsolicited telemarketing calls from BT Wholesale and other companies, please contact BT Wholesale Direct on 0800 671045 and register your telephone number(s). Direct marketing calls should stop after 28 days.
